A Guide to the Gubernatorial Appointments of the Virginia Secretary of Commonwealth, 1994-2017 (bulk 2002-2008)
Library of Virginia
- Transportation, Virginia Commercial Spaceflight Authority 2003-2008 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Veterans Affairs, Board of Veterans Services, 2003-2008 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Veterans Affairs, Veterans Services Foundation, 2003-2008 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Veterans Affairs, Virginia War Memorial Foundation, Board of Trustees, 2002-2008 (Box 17, Folder 3)